Guide to the First Congregational Church of Portland records 1849-2016
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- General records, 1850-2015; Series A
  - Reports, Subseries 6
    - Annual Reports 1959, 1960 January 19 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Annual Reports 1960, 1961 January 17 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Annual Reports 1961, 1962 January 16 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Annual Reports 1962, 1963 January 15 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Annual Reports 1963, 1964 January 28 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Annual reports for 1964, 1965 January 19 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Annual reports for 1965, 1966 January 18 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Annual reports for 1966, 1967 January 17 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Annual reports for 1967, 1968 January 16 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Annual reports for 1968, 1969 January 21 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Annual reports for 1969, 1970 January 20 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Annual reports for 1970, 1971 January 19 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Annual reports for 1971, 1972 January 18 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Annual reports for 1972, 1973 January 16 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Annual reports for 1973, 1974 January 20 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Annual reports for 1974, 1975 January 19 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Annual reports for 1975, 1976 January 18 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Annual reports for 1976, 1977 January 23 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Annual reports for 1977, 1978 January 22 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Annual reports for 1978, 1979 January (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Annual reports for 1979, 1980 January 27 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Annual Report 1981, 1981 January 25 (Box-folder 21/3)
      Reports for the year 1980.
    - Annual Report 1982, 1982 January 31 (Box-folder 21/4)
      Reports for the year 1981.
    - Annual Report 1983, 1983 January 23 (Box-folder 21/5)
      Reports for the year 1982.
    - Annual Report 1984, 1984 January 29 (Box-folder 21/6)
      Reports for the year 1983.
    - Annual Report 1985, 1985 January 27 (Box-folder 21/7)
      Reports for the year 1984.
    - Annual Report 1986, 1986 January 26 (Box-folder 21/8)
      Reports for the year 1985.
    - Annual Report 1987, 1987 January 18 (Box-folder 21/9)
      Reports for the year 1986.
    - Annual Report 1988, 1988 January 24 (Box-folder 21/10)
      Reports for the year 1987.
    - Annual Report 1988, 1989 January 29 (Box-folder 21/11)
      Reports for the year 1988.
    - Annual Report 1989, 1990 January 28 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Annual Report 1990, 1991 January 27 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Annual Report 1991, 1992 January 26 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Annual Report 1992, 1993 January 24 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Annual Report 1993, 1994 January 30 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Annual Report 1994, 1995 February 5 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Annual Report 1995, 1996 January 28 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Annual Report 1996, 1997 January 26 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Annual Report 1998, 1998 June 7 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 1999 June 13 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 1999 September 19 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2000 June 4 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2001 May 20 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2002 June 9 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2003 June 8 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2004 June 6 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2005 June 5 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2006 June 11 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Annual Meeting reports, 2007 June 3 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Annual Report 2007-2008, 2008 May 4 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Annual Report 2008-2009, 2009 June 7 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Annual Report 2009-2010, 2010 June 6 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Historian's report for 1903, circa 1904 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Moderator's Report to Council, 2013 February (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Pastor's assistant reports, circa 1922-1924 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Pastor's reports, 1961, 1963 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Pastor's reports, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Pastor's reports, 1966, 1970 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Minister's reports, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Assistant Minister's reports, 2013-2014 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Summary reports, 2008 October 13 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Report by unidentified "representative of one branch of Oregon's most important industries", circa 1921 (Box-folder 23/15)
  - Resignations from Board of Trustees, 1894-1895 (Box-folder 23/16)
  - Resolution made upon death of Dr. Cephas F. Clapp, 1920 October 28 (Box-folder 23/17)
  - Sermons delivered by visiting ministers, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 23/18)
  - Sermonette, "Youth in the Church", 1958 January 25 (Box-folder 23/19)
    Delivered by Charla Woodworth.
  - Signup sheet for greeters and coffee servers, 1991 October (Box-folder 23/20)
  - Survey of organists' wedding fees at downtown Portland churches, 1981 June (Box-folder 23/21)
  - Clipping re Thanksgiving celebration, 1989 (Box-folder 23/22)
  - Documents, clippings, etc. re Thanksgiving and Pilgrims, 1935-1993 (Box-folder 23/23-23/24)
    Materials removed from a binder and kept in original order.
  - Documents re Thanksgiving and Pilgrims - Transcript of Howard H. Campbell's speech to Business and Professional Women's Club, 1986 October 11 (Box-folder 24/1)
    Speech had been at back of the binder containing the materials in folders 23/24-23/25.
  - Flyer for training event, 1977 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Documents re volunteer appreciation (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Wedding brochure, circa 1981 (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Wedding rehearsal suggestions, 1969 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - "1987 Youth as Leaders" workshop descriptions (Box-folder 24/6)
- Groups, 1863-2015; Series B
  Records, correspondence, and ephemera relating to commissions, committees, and other organized groups within First Congregational Church of Portland.
  - 35-Year Club, Subseries 1
    Organization of people who had been members of the First Congregational Church for 35 years or longer.
    - By-laws, circa 1931 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Clippings re 35-Year Club (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1931-1938 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1940-1951 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Correspondence and records re Centennial Fund and "Historical Niche", 1950-1953 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Financial accounting of annual dinner, 1957 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Program for dinner on George H. Himes' 90th birthday, 1934 May 18 (Box-folder 24/16)
      Additional copies of program located in 59/3.
    - Annual Meeting/Dinner agendas and minutes, 1930-circa 1955 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Annual Meeting agendas and minutes, 1941-1959 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Annual Meeting minutes and reports, 1942-1962 (Box-folder 24/19)
      Bound volume.
    - Summation of annual meetings for 1942-1952, circa 1953 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Annual Meeting agendas and minutes, 1963-1968, 1976 (Box-folder 24/21)
    - Motion re Lurah Himes Memorial Fund, undated (Box-folder 24/22)
    - Officer nominations, 1950 June 20 (Box-folder 24/23)
    - Record book, 1962-1972 (Box-folder 24/24)
    - Annual reports, 1944-1954 (Box-folder 24/25)
    - Annual reports, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 24/26)
    - Historian's report, 1962 June 19 (Box-folder 24/27)
    - Roster of charter members, 1930 (Box-folder 24/28)
    - Rosters, 1931-1937 (Box-folder 24/29)
    - Rosters, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 24/30)
    - Rosters, 1950-1961 (Box-folder 24/31)
    - Roster, circa 1955 (Box-folder 24/32)
    - Roster of new members and officers, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 24/33)
    - Rosters, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 24/34)
    - Rosters and mailing lists, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24/35)
    - Dinner speeches, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 24/36)
  - Artreach, Subseries 2
    See also Series M: Performing and visual arts
    - Records re "Art Among Us" art show, 2012 July (Box-folder 24/37)
    - Artist profiles, circa 1990 (Box-folder 24/38)
    - Blank form for commission of artist sales, circa 2010 (Box-folder 24/39)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 24/40)
    - Finances- budgets and proposed budgets, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 24/41)
    - Meeting minutes, 1985 September-1986 (Box-folder 24/42)
    - Meeting minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1994-1996; 2002; undated (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Reports, 2007-2015 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Rosters, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Arts and Appointments Committee records, 1968 March (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Arts Committee - 1986 budget request, circa 1985 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Audit Committee reports, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Budget and Stewardship Committee meeting minutes, 1972 December 19 (Box-folder 25/9)
  - Building Committee - cash and journal, 1889-1898 (Box-folder 114/3)
  - Building Committee - ledger, circa 1890-1898 (Box-folder 114/2)
  - Buildings and Grounds Commission meeting minutes and reports, 2011 October-2014 (Box-folder 25/10)
  - Business and Professional Women's Club, Subseries 3
    Includes records of the predecessor group Valencia Club.
    - Research files (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Proposed changes to by-laws, 1969 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Proposed amendment to by-laws, 1977 February 12 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Notes for Christmas luncheon, circa 1975 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Constitution, 1945 April 13 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1965 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Suggested changes to constitution, 1972 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Correspondence, 1944; 1951-1957 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Correspondence - letter re luncheon costs and list of letter's recipients, 1973 October 17 (Box-folder 25/20)
    - Correspondence - letters to Senators Mark Hatfield and Bob Packwood, 1976 April 10 (Box-folder 25/21)
      Letter requested that the senators introduce a bill to change the national anthem to "America the Beautiful."
    - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - Membership directories, 1969-1970; 1974-1975 (Box-folder 25/23)
    - Membership directories, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 25/24)
    - Finances - Treasurer's reports, 1948; 1956-1959 (Box-folder 25/25)
    - Histories of Business and Professional Women's Club, 1960 March 17; 1975 March 8 (Box-folder 25/26)
    - Scrapbook re history of Business and Professional Women's Club, 1938-1953 (Box-folder Box 130)
    - Scrapbook re history of Business and Professional Women's Club, 1952-1962 (Box-folder Box 131)
    - Scrapbook re history of Business and Professional Women's Club, 1964-1983 (Box-folder Box 132)
    - Memorandum and program calendar, 1981 (Box-folder 25/27)
    - Meeting minutes, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 25/28)
    - Meeting minutes, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Meeting minutes, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Meeting minutes, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Meeting minutes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Meeting minutes, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Meeting minutes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Meeting minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Meeting minutes, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 26/16)
    - Meeting minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 26/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 26/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 26/19)
    - Meeting minutes, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 26/20)
    - Meeting minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 26/21)
    - Meeting minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Meeting notices, 1938-1948 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Moderator's message, 1992 October (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Nominations, 1950 March 10 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Annual reports, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Annual report of Library Committee, 1982 March (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Reports re summer outings/picnics, 1947-1948; 1951; 1958 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Reports re summer outings/picnics, 1964; 1969; 1971; 1975 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Rosters, 1939; 1943; 1947-1948 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Membership and committee rosters, 1943-1950 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Rosters, 1950-1957 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Membership and committee rosters, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - Slate of officers, 1978 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Valencia Club records book, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Report of Valencia Club for 1944, circa 1945 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Camera Club, Subseries 4
    - Clipping re Camera Club, 1955 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - Constitution, circa 1950 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - Correspondence - Letter from Reverend Lincoln Y. Reed to Marguerite Oliver re Camera Club ministry at Ray Holmes' memorial service, 1981 June 26 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - Directory/calendars, 1952; 1959; 1966 (Box-folder 27/22)
    - Directory/calendars, 1972; 1975-1978 (Box-folder 27/23)
    - Directory/calendars, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 27/24)
    - Histories of Camera Club, 1991; undated (Box-folder 27/25)
    - Annual reports, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 27/26)
    - Roster, 1984 (Box-folder 27/27)
  - Caregivers Committee records, 1991 (Box-folder 27/28)
  - Christian Action Commission, Subseries 5
    - Section of bylaws re Christian Action, 1974 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Materials re chemical weapons, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 27/30)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 27/31)
    - Correspondence and documents re Angela Davis controversy, 1972 (Box-folder 27/32)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 27/33)
    - Correspondence from Downtown Ministries, 1987 (Box-folder 27/34)
    - Correspondence logs, 1988 March-April (Box-folder 27/35)
    - Correspondence and records re donation campaigns and designated offerings, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 27/36)
    - Records re Downtown Churches Lunch Center, 1983-1987; undated (Box-folder 27/37)
    - Event flyers and notices, 1964; 1982; 1991-1992 (Box-folder 27/38)
    - Finances - Budgets and budget proposals, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 27/39)
    - Finances - Budgets and budget proposals, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 27/40)
    - "The Four Types of Social Concern" by Thomas E. Price, 1973 April (Box-folder 27/41)
    - Goals and suggested actions, circa 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/42)
    - List of "Hub-Cap" programs in West Burnside area, 1972 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Mailing re "Christian Action Program", 1966 September 14 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Memo re Forecourt Fountain controversy, 1972 July 31 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Memo re 1990 United Church of Christ Just Peace Appeal, 1989 December 26 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - "Meet the Candidates" programs, 1970 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1965 October-1966 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Meeting minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Meeting minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Meeting minutes, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Meeting minutes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 28/12)
    - Meeting minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 28/13)
      Includes attached documents.
    - Meeting minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - Meeting minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Meeting minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - Meeting minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - Meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 28/19)
    - Meeting minutes, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28/20)
    - Resume of pact meeting at Camp Adams, 1972 January (Box-folder 28/21)
    - Materials re Northwest Pilot Project and assistance for the homeless, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 28/22)
    - Priorities and resolutions, 1988 (Box-folder 28/23)
    - Racial justice issues, circa 1964; 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28/24)
    - Materials re refugees, 1985 (Box-folder 28/25)
    - Report, 1981 September 21 (Box-folder 28/26)
    - Rosters, 1966-1972; 1978-1979 (Box-folder 28/27)
    - Rosters, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 28/28)
    - Schedule for planning retreat at Camp Adams, 1988 (Box-folder 28/29)
    - Staffing proposal for Urban Ministries Coordinator, 1984 December 4 (Box-folder 28/30)
    - Correspondence and records re sponsorship of South Korean students, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 28/31)
  - Christian Education Commission, Subseries 6
    See also Series O: Sunday School and church education.
    - Brochures, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Bulletins, flyers, etc., 1954-1955 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - "Program Emphases" calendar, 1970 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Events calendar, "A First Youth Look Ahead.. .", 1986 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Correspondence and memos, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Correspondence by and about Jim Staal, 1986 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Pre-school study group evaluation sheet, 1966 May 17 (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Evaluation of Learning Community workshop, Everett, Washington, 1973 October (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Evaluation of Advent/Christmas program, 1981 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Finances - Purchase authorization request, 1958 August 21 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - Finances - Proposed budgets, 1972-1974; 1982 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Flyers for events, 1970 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Flyers, memos, and programs for events, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Group and event flyers, 1991-circa 1995 (Box-folder 29/15)
    - Friends lists, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 29/16)
    - Information for church school teachers, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 29/17)
    - Invitation form for church school teaching, 1991 June (Box-folder 29/18)
    - Job descriptions for subcommittees, 1972 February 2 (Box-folder 29/19)
    - "Learning Opportunities 1973-1974" (Box-folder 29/20)
    - Letter to teachers and attached attendance records, 1994 (Box-folder 29/21)
    - Clippings re Ruth McClun, 1954 (Box-folder 29/22)
    - Memo from Ruth Zilk to church school teachers, 1966 June 3 (Box-folder 29/23)
    - Memos re events and classes, 1984 (Box-folder 29/24)
    - Memos, 1991 April-May (Box-folder 29/25)
    - Teachers and officers meeting minutes, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 29/26)
    - Meeting minutes, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 29/27)
    - Meeting minutes, 1965 October-1969 (Box-folder 29/28)
    - Meeting minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 29/29)
    - Meeting minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 29/30)
    - Meeting minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 29/31)
    - Meeting minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 29/32)
    - Meeting minutes, 1974-1975 June (Box-folder 29/33)
    - Meeting minutes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29/34)
    - Meeting minutes, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 29/35)
    - Meeting minutes, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 29/36)
    - Meeting minutes, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 29/37)
    - Meeting minutes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Meeting minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Meeting minutes, 1999; 2001-2003; 2006 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Meeting minutes and reports, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee meeting agendas and recommendations, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Children's Work Committee meeting minutes, 1960; 1965; 1968 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Parents' meeting minutes, 2002 March 2 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Newsletters/bulletins, 1951-1955; 1959 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - "Open Minds" newsletters, 1986 (Box-folder 30/11)
      Also includes attached letters written by Jim Staal.
    - "Youth Tidings" newsletters, 1934 February (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Notes from meeting with Jim Staal, 1986 July (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Notices about events, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - Notices, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 30/15)
    - Objectives, 1955 September (Box-folder 30/16)
    - Organization of the church school, circa 1953 (Box-folder 30/17)
    - Policy on teenage drivers, 1973 (Box-folder 30/18)
    - Proposals and resolutions, 1982; 1985 (Box-folder 30/19)
    - Church school questionnaire, 1955 September 13 (Box-folder 30/20)
    - Teachers questionnaires, 1995 January (Box-folder 30/21)
    - Reports of church school, 1921-1926 (Box-folder 30/22)
    - Reports, 1937; 1947; 1965 (Box-folder 30/23)
    - Report, 1987 November 18 (Box-folder 30/24)
    - Adult Committee report, 1965 April 5 (Box-folder 30/25)
    - Building and Finance Committee report, circa 1960 (Box-folder 30/26)
    - Associate minister's reports, 1966 October 4; 1968 June 3 (Box-folder 30/27)
    - Report by Ruth Zilk, 1966 April 5 (Box-folder 30/28)
    - Retreats and trips, 1971-1973; 1982; 1987 (Box-folder 30/29)
    - Retreat and picnic, 1991 (Box-folder 30/30)
    - Retreat, 1996 June (Box-folder 30/31)
    - Rosters, 1966-1991 (Box-folder 30/32)
    - Sex education, 1973 (Box-folder 30/33)
    - Space needs, circa 1963 (Box-folder 30/34)
    - Space and building change requests, 1966 (Box-folder 30/35)
    - Statement of purpose, 1982 March 2 (Box-folder 30/36)
    - Clipping re Faye A. Steinmetz, 1934 (Box-folder 30/37)
    - Study course, "The Pre-Teen Child", 1973 (Box-folder 30/38)
    - Summary of course, "World Affairs and Our Christian Responsibility", 1954 (Box-folder 30/39)
    - Summary of Rooms and Equipment Committee meeting, 1954 June (Box-folder 30/40)
    - Adult education survey, 1997 January (Box-folder 30/41)
    - Twenty-something/thirty-something mailing list and attached letter, circa 1992 (Box-folder 30/42)
    - Youth Subcommittee meeting minutes, 1971 October 18 (Box-folder 30/43)
  - Christian Endeavor, Subseries 7
    Includes materials relating to Junior Christian Endeavor, Intermediate Christian Endeavor, Senior Christian Endeavor, and Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor (Y.P.S.C.E.).
    - Prayer meeting topic calendars, 1883-1884; circa 1889 (Box-folder 30/44)
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor constitution and by-laws, circa 1895 (Box-folder 30/45)
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor directory/calendars, 1892; 1897-1899 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor directory/calendars, 1900-1909; 1913 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Ephemera, circa 1895; circa 1906 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Event programs, 1895-1899 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Event programs, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Program of entertainment event by Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor (Box-folder 112/6)
    - Programs for exercises, 1897-1899 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor finances and reports, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Letter re fundraising for travel to International Christian Endeavor Convention in San Francisco, California, 1931 July 8 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - Minutes book of Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor, 1901 September 3 - 1902 March 9; 1920 November (Box-folder 31/9)
      Book also includes constitution and by-laws of Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor.
    - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor meeting minutes, 1913-1917 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Membership records book, 1930-1932 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Amiciatiae Intermediate Christian Endeavor membership book, 1919 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Newsletters - issues of Christian Endeavor Bulletin, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 31/13)